<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our services on Status Artis Construction</title><link>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/</link><description>Recent content in Our services on Status Artis Construction</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 06:46:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://statusartis.gr/en/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>House Construction</title><link>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/house-construction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/house-construction/</guid><description>At Status Artis we offer comprehensive services of design, supervision and construction of houses (turnkey). We create constructions with high aesthetics, functional spaces and mainly energy autonomy. We are particularly focused on low energy footprint buildings, proposing and implementing the most modern energy saving solutions.
In the context of our cooperation with you:
We present you alternative proposals in 3D for your new property and we modify them according to your needs and desires.</description></item><item><title>House and businesses renovations</title><link>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/house-renovation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/house-renovation/</guid><description>At Status Artis we undertake all types of renovation and renovation of homes and businesses. We have perfectly coordinated workshops in order to complete the work in the shortest possible time. This is also the most important issue in the renovations, taking into account your needs for the short reopening of the space to be renovated.
In the context of our cooperation with you:
We first capture your space and discuss your needs and desires together.</description></item><item><title>Energy upgrade of buildings</title><link>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/insulation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 06:46:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/insulation/</guid><description>By upgrading the energy of a building, the quality of life of the tenants is improved, the heating and cooling costs are minimized and the damage to the building is reduced.
To upgrade the energy class of a building, you need:
Thermal insulation of the roof 🡪 It is the most important thermal insulation of the building. More than 50% of a building&amp;rsquo;s heat loss is due to a lack of proper roof insulation.</description></item><item><title>Solving building problems</title><link>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/electrical-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 06:44:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/electrical-work/</guid><description>To successfully deal with a building problem, the exact location of the real source of the problem is paramount. At Status Artis, during our long tenure in Sweden, we have invested in a number of measuring and detection instruments, so that we can successfully undertake the final solution of building problems such as:
Moisture and mold Water inflows inside the house Cracks from earthquakes Damage to the outside of the building Hydraulic leaks Electrical problems Noise pollution Our company undertakes insulation, waterproofing, building reinforcement, thermal insulation, thermal facade, repair of plumbing and electrical installations and sound insulation.</description></item><item><title>Custom designs</title><link>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/custom-designs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 06:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://statusartis.gr/en/services/custom-designs/</guid><description>At Status Artis we have precision cutting machines (fiber laser and CNC router) for wood, plastic and metal, for the creation of special constructions (furniture, railings, partitions, metal facades of buildings, etc.) that give a unique character to each space.</description></item></channel></rss>